{
    "subject": "resource/Jari_Tolsa",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Espoo_Blues_players",
    "human_readable": "Jari Tolsa's topic of expertise is Category:Espoo Blues players.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.907177746295929,
            "question": "What type of players are categorized by Jari Tolsa's expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8588855266571045,
            "question": "What is the name of the category related to Jari Tolsa's expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8442732095718384,
            "question": "To which category does Jari Tlosa's expertise belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8422016501426697,
            "question": "What is the connection between Jari Tolsa and Espoo Blues players?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8133288621902466,
            "question": "What is Jari Tolsa an expert on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6505799889564514,
            "question": "Who are Espoo Blues players?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6174474954605103,
            "question": "In what area does Jari Tolsa specialize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6027377843856812,
            "question": "Can you describe Jari Tolsa's area of knowledge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5901715755462646,
            "question": "What do Espoo Blues players represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4165199398994446,
            "question": "What is the field of study related to Jari Tolsa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jari Tolsa's topic of expertise is Category:Espoo Blues players.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1954_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do Espoo Blues players represent?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1954_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe Jari Tolsa's area of knowledge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1954_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what area does Jari Tolsa specialize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1954_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1954_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the triple \"Fr\u00f6lunda uses what they call an integrated approach in their player development\" supports the statement.\n\nHere is my evaluation:\n\n{ \n  \"output\": \"yes\" \n} \n\nThe documents mention that Fr\u00f6lunda uses an \"integrated approach\" in their player development (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1954/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt), which has three principal components. This information supports the statement, so the value should be \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n- The provided documents do not contain any information related to Jari Tolsa or his expertise in the context of Espoo Blues players, nor does it mention the Nobel Prize in Literature. Therefore, the query cannot be supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Query: Calle Johansson played for Fr\u00f6lunda HC.\n   Response: {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"no\"}\n\nThe given context does not contain any information related to Jari Tolsa or his expertise as an Espoo Blues player. Therefore, the provided query cannot be verified based on the documents."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Jari Tolsa or Espoo Blues players in the provided text.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Jari Tolsa or Espoo Blues players, making the statement about his topic of expertise unrelated and unsupported by the given details.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}